wi-tribe.pk 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | wi-tribe

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, wi-tribe Pakistan Limited provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where we request personally-identifiable information.

 **Scope of this Privacy Notice**  
This privacy notice (this “Privacy Notice”) applies only to information collected at the website www.wi-tribe.pk (“Website”), which is owned and operated by wi-tribe Pakistan Limited (“wi-tribe”). This Privacy Notice does not apply to other websites owned or operated by wi-tribe, nor to any websites owned or operated by affiliated wi-tribe companies, including wi-tribe limited – Jordan PSC or wi-tribe limited. In addition, this Privacy Notice does not apply to websites linked to wi-tribe.com or websites owned or operated by companies with whom wi-tribe does business. To learn how these websites collect, use, and safeguard your personal information, please consult their privacy notices.

 **The Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
Browsing this Website does not require you to give us any personally-identifiable information; however, you may choose to give us contact and certain other personally-identifiable information so that you can take advantage of some of our services. For example, you may want to contact us, email one of our web pages to someone, or apply for a job with us. When you do these things, we will ask you for personally-identifiable information, which we will use to process your requests.

In addition, we may use the contact information that you provide us to send you news or promotional information that we believe may be of interest to you. Should you no longer wish to receive these mailings from wi-tribe, you may opt-out of receiving them at any time. To opt-out; please send us a brief email at [media@wi-tribe.pk](mailto:media@wi-tribe.pk,ali.fahd@pk.wi-tribe.com,faraz.niaz@pk.wi-tribe.com) telling us to remove you from our mailing list.

If you apply for a job through our Website, we require that you provide certain personally-identifiable information, including your name, contact information, gender, date of birth, and a curriculum vitae. wi-tribe treats this information as confidential and uses it only to consider you for employment. wi-tribe does not share this information except, as described below.

Personally-identifiable information submitted to the Website may be shared with wi-tribe affiliates. In addition, wi-tribe may share this information with certain third-party service providers, which wi-tribe uses to fulfill or hasten your requests. wi-tribe does not sell or otherwise share your personally-identifiable information.  
wi-tribe also collects statistical information about the users of our Website. wi-tribe aggregates this information and does not link it to personally-identifiable information. wi-tribe uses this information to help diagnose problems with our server and administer our Website, to analyze trends, to track use and movement around the Website, and to gather broad demographic information about our users. wi-tribe collects this information using log files, cookies, and web beacons.

 **Log Files**  
As is true of most websites, wi-tribe gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. wi-tribe does not link the information we store in log files to any personally-identifiable information you submit while on our Website.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. wi-tribe uses session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Website. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. wi-tribe does not link the information we store in cookies to any personally-identifiable information you submit while on our Website.

 **Clear Gifs**  
We employ a software technology, called clear gifs (also called web beacons or web bugs), that helps us better manage the content on our Website by informing us of what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally-identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  
Ownership of Information

wi-tribe is the sole owner of the information collected on wi-tribe.pk; any information you submit is completely voluntary.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally-identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

 **Links to Other Sites**  
This Website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by wi-tribe. Please be aware that wi-tribe is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites.

 **Business Transitions**  
In the event that wi-tribe goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally-identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

 **Changes in this Privacy Notice**  
If wi-tribe decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Notice, the homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so that you can know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

wi-tribe reserves the right to modify this Privacy Notice at any time, so please review it frequently. If wi-tribe makes material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our home page.
